A Guide to the John C. Bugher papers FA027
Rockefeller Archive Center
- General Files, 1
  - General Files - Post 1950, 1950-1968; 2
    - A. J. Cipriani, n.d. (Box 14, Folder 179)
    - Civil Defense, 1961-1965 (Box 14, Folder 180)
      Shelters, self protection. L. J. Deal.
    - Civil Defense - Reports, n.d. (Box 14, Folder 181)
    - Civil Defense - Reports, n.d. (Box 14, Folder 182)
    - Harlan Cleveland, 1956 (Box 14, Folder 183)
    - Amador Cobas, 1959-1960 (Box 14, Folder 184)
    - William C. Cobb, 1961-1965 (Box 14, Folder 185)
    - Sterling Coe, 1955-1956 (Box 14, Folder 186)
    - Committee on New Frontiers of Technology, 1960-January 1961 (Box 14, Folder 187)
      Chamber of Commerce. Interdisciplinary contribution and solution of pressing problems.
    - Committee on New Frontiers of Technology, 1960-January 1961 (Box 14, Folder 188)
    - Committee on New Frontiers of Technology - Reports, n.d. (Box 15, Folder 189)
    - Robert Condon, 1960 (Box 15, Folder 190)
    - J. Frank Coneybear, 1964 (Box 15, Folder 191)
    - Conference on Geochronology of Rock Systems, n.d. (Box 15, Folder 192)
    - Conference on Health Information Retrieval, 1959-1960 (Box 15, Folder 193)
    - Robert Conrad, 1962 (Box 15, Folder 194)
    - Robert Corsbie, 1960-1964 (Box 15, Folder 195)
      National Institute for Disaster Mobilization, civil defense systems design, civil effects test operations.
    - Cosmos Club, 1955-1963 (Box 15, Folder 196)
    - George Cotzias, 1958 (Box 15, Folder 197)
    - J. Coursaget, 1960 (Box 15, Folder 198)
    - Palmer H. Craig, 1962 (Box 15, Folder 199)
    - Adele Croninger, 1957 (Box 15, Folder 200)
    - Eugene Cronkite, 1955 (Box 15, Folder 201)
    - Maxwell Dauer, 1966 (Box 15, Folder 202)
    - Elbert de Coursey, 1956 (Box 15, Folder 203)
    - Alfred B. Demiston, 1956 (Box 15, Folder 204)
    - Diary, 1958-1960 (Box 15, Folder 205)
    - Diary, 1958-1960 (Box 15, Folder 206)
    - Diary - Unrecorded Interviews, 1958-1959 (Box 15, Folder 207)
    - G. J. Dienes, 1965 (Box 16, Folder 208)
    - Peter Dohrn, 1959 (Box 16, Folder 209)
    - E. A. Doisy, 1956-1966 (Box 16, Folder 210)
    - P. Dorolle, 1955-1956 (Box 16, Folder 211)
    - Wilbur G. Downs, 1964 (Box 16, Folder 212)
    - Robert Dudley, 1956-1959 (Box 16, Folder 213)
      Atomic energy in Egypt.
    - Charles L. Dunham, 1959-1960 (Box 16, Folder 214)
    - Lucia Dunham, 1959 (Box 16, Folder 215)
    - Gordon Dunning, 1959 (Box 16, Folder 216)
    - William Durrett, 1957 (Box 16, Folder 217)
    - Merrill Eisenbud, 1960 (Box 16, Folder 218)
    - Milton S. Eisenhower, 1959 (Box 16, Folder 219)
    - Sigvaard Eklund, 1960 (Box 16, Folder 220)
    - G. A. Elliott, 1957 (Box 16, Folder 221)
    - Basil Elms, n.d. (Box 16, Folder 222)
    - "Encyclopedia Britannica", n.d. (Box 16, Folder 223)
    - Giaocchino Failla, 1959-1960 (Box 16, Folder 224)
    - Fairleigh Dickinson University, 1959-1960 (Box 16, Folder 225)
    - James Fairman, 1959 (Box 16, Folder 226)
    - Raymond Farwall, 1959 (Box 16, Folder 227)
    - T. J. Finch, 1957 (Box 16, Folder 228)
    - Paul F. Foster, 1963-1964 (Box 16, Folder 229)
      Regional centers for reactors; International Atomic Energy Agency. A. A. Wells.
    - Roberto Franco, 1957 (Box 16, Folder 230)
    - James French, 1960-1966 (Box 16, Folder 231)
    - Walter Friend, 1959-1960 (Box 16, Folder 232)
    - Andreas Fritzeche, 1960 (Box 16, Folder 233)
    - Hisaji Fukatsu, 1956 (Box 16, Folder 234)
    - Arnoldo Gabaldon, 1959 (Box 16, Folder 235)
    - John Gentry, 1959 (Box 16, Folder 236)
    - Luc Gillon, 1960 (Box 16, Folder 237)
    - Raymond Gilmore, 1955-1960 (Box 16, Folder 238)
    - Alan Gilroy, 1957 (Box 16, Folder 239)
    - Keith Glennan, 1960 (Box 16, Folder 240)
    - Julien Goens, 1960 (Box 16, Folder 241)
    - Bertand Goldschmidt, 1960 (Box 16, Folder 242)
    - Gordon Research Conference - Toxicology and Safety Evaluation, 1957 (Box 16, Folder 243)
      Participant.
    - Isaac Gonzalez-Martinez, 1960 (Box 16, Folder 244)
    - Denise Grant, 1957 (Box 16, Folder 245)
    - John B. Grant, 1957-1962 (Box 16, Folder 246)
      Puerto Rico Public Health; university hospital.
    - Lucien Gregg, 1959 (Box 16, Folder 247)
    - Luis Gutierrez, 1960 (Box 16, Folder 248)
    - Lewis W. Hackett, 1960 (Box 16, Folder 249)
    - James Haggerty, 1959-1960 (Box 16, Folder 250)
    - Richard Hahn, 1951-1956 (Box 16, Folder 251)
    - Howard Hall, 1960 (Box 16, Folder 252)
    - John Hall, 1959 (Box 16, Folder 253)
    - Walter Hamilton, 1960 (Box 16, Folder 254)
    - J. G. Harrar, 1960-1966 (Box 16, Folder 255)
      University development; ecology; virology.
    - P. D. Hartzer, 1960 (Box 17, Folder 256)
    - James Hautgering, 1960 (Box 17, Folder 257)
    - Lee Haworth, 1960 (Box 17, Folder 258)
    - Guy S. Hayes, 1959 (Box 17, Folder 259)
    - J. W. Healey, 1959 (Box 17, Folder 260)
    - Health and Safety Laboratory, 1959-1966 (Box 17, Folder 261)
    - Health Research Council, 1960 (Box 17, Folder 262)
    - Roderick Heffron, 1959 (Box 17, Folder 263)
    - Louis Hempelmann, 1960 (Box 17, Folder 264)
    - George Herrmann, 1960 (Box 17, Folder 265)
    - R. T. Hewitt, 1960 (Box 17, Folder 266)
    - Robert Heyssel, 1960 (Box 17, Folder 267)
    - Norman Hillberry, 1960 (Box 17, Folder 268)
    - Dr. Hilleboe, 1959 (Box 17, Folder 269)
    - Yoshio Hiyama, 1956 (Box 17, Folder 270)
      Marine biology; radiation.
    - F. J. Hodges, 1960 (Box 17, Folder 271)
    - Jules Horowitz, 1960 (Box 17, Folder 272)
    - Frank Horsfall, 1960 (Box 17, Folder 273)
    - James Horsfall, 1960 (Box 17, Folder 274)
    - Infant Mortality, n.d. (Box 17, Folder 275)
    - India - Africa Trip, 1956-1957 (Box 17, Folder 276)
      Dedication of Indian atomic energy facility; virology; demography.
    - India - Africa Trip - Reprints (Box 17, Folder 277)
    - India - Africa Trip - Reprints (Box 18, Folder 278)
    - India - Africa Trip - Reprints (Box 18, Folder 279)
    - Industrial Nuclear Technology Conference, 1956 (Box 18, Folder 280)
    - "Information Storage, Recall and Transmission ina Medical Library System", 1956 (Box 18, Folder 281)
    - Information Storage and Retrieval, 1955-1960 (Box 18, Folder 282)
    - International Atomic Energy Agency, 1960-1963 (Box 18, Folder 283)
    - International Brotherhood of Electrical Workers, Local 160, 1956-1957 (Box 18, Folder 284)
    - International Conference on the Peaceful Uses of Atomic Energy, 1955-1956 (Box 18, Folder 285)
    - International Journal of Applied Radiation and Isotopes, 1955-1959 (Box 18, Folder 286)
      Advisory Editorial Board.
    - John Janney, 1955-1958 (Box 18, Folder 287)
    - Warren C. Johnson, 1959-1960 (Box 18, Folder 288)
    - Joint Committee on Atomic Energy, 1960-1962 (Box 18, Folder 289)
    - Joint Committee on Atomic Energy - Reports, Hearings, n.d. (Box 18, Folder 290)
    - Joint Committee on Atomic Energy - Reports, n.d. (Box 19, Folder 291)
    - Joint Council on Economic Education, 1958 (Box 19, Folder 292)
    - Hardin Jones, 1955-1957 (Box 19, Folder 293)
    - Hardin Jones - Reports, n.d. (Box 19, Folder 294)
    - Hardin Jones - Reports, n.d. (Box 19, Folder 295)
    - Journal of Medical Education, 1959 (Box 19, Folder 296)
    - Olav Kaasa, 1960 (Box 19, Folder 297)
    - Haruo Katsunuma, 1959 (Box 19, Folder 298)
    - Harold A. Knapp, 1961 (Box 19, Folder 299)
    - Fred W. Knipe, 1960 (Box 19, Folder 300)
    - Don Koenig, 1957 (Box 19, Folder 301)
    - Ted Koenig, 1956 (Box 19, Folder 302)
    - Robert H. Kokernot, 1962 (Box 19, Folder 303)
      Colombia virus program.
    - Harry Kornberg, 1959 (Box 19, Folder 304)
    - Laboratory Notebook, 1963 (Box 19, Folder 305)
    - Wright Langham, 1957-1960 (Box 19, Folder 306)
    - Mrs. Albert Lasker, 1959-1960 (Box 19, Folder 307)
    - John H. Lawrence, 1960 (Box 19, Folder 308)
    - Roger Leatherman, 1959 (Box 19, Folder 309)
    - Hugh Leavell, 1959 (Box 19, Folder 310)
    - Leonard Leaderman, 1960 (Box 20, Folder 311)
    - Paul Le Fevre, 1959-1960 (Box 20, Folder 312)
    - George Le Roy, 1960 (Box 20, Folder 313)
    - Leukemia, 1957 (Box 20, Folder 314)
    - W. F. Libby, 1959 (Box 20, Folder 315)
    - Vernon Lippard, 1960 (Box 20, Folder 316)
    - Herman Lisco, 1960-1963 (Box 20, Folder 317)
      Cancer of cervix; leukemia.
    - William Looney, 1957-1959 (Box 20, Folder 318)
    - John Loutit, 1957-1959 (Box 20, Folder 319)
    - A. H. Lovell, 1957 (Box 20, Folder 320)
    - Alvin Luedecke, 1959-1964 (Box 20, Folder 321)
    - Colin MacLeod, 1959-1960 (Box 20, Folder 322)
    - Francis N. MacNamara, 1953-1959 (Box 20, Folder 323)
    - O. S. Macnamara, 1958 (Box 20, Folder 324)
    - A. H. Mahaffy, 1955-1956 (Box 20, Folder 325)
    - B. Malamos, 1960 (Box 20, Folder 326)
    - V. S. Mangalik, 1957 (Box 20, Folder 327)
    - John Manley, 1960 (Box 20, Folder 328)
    - L. D. Marinelli, 1959 (Box 20, Folder 329)
    - John Marshall, 1960 (Box 20, Folder 330)
    - Hareo Matsuyame, 1960 (Box 20, Folder 331)
    - Myles Maxfield, 1957 (Box 20, Folder 332)
    - I. B. Maxwell, 1957-1959 (Box 20, Folder 333)
    - Russell Maynard, 1957 (Box 20, Folder 334)
    - Mayor's Technical Advisory Committee on Radiation, 1959 (Box 20, Folder 335)
      New York City.
    - N. F. McCann, 1955 (Box 20, Folder 336)
    - Joseph L. McCarthy, 1960 (Box 20, Folder 337)
    - John A. McCone, 1959-1960 (Box 20, Folder 338)
    - J. B. McCormick, 1959-1960 (Box 20, Folder 339)
    - Frank McCune, 1959 (Box 20, Folder 340)
    - Paul McDaniel, 1960 (Box 20, Folder 341)
    - Medical Radio System, 1960 (Box 20, Folder 342)
      Post-graduate medical education.
    - Memoranda, 1951-1960 (Box 20, Folder 343)
    - Memoranda, 1951-1960 (Box 20, Folder 344)
    - Memoranda, 1951-1960 (Box 20, Folder 345)
    - Memoranda, 1951-1960 (Box 20, Folder 346)
    - Memoranda, 1951-1960 (Box 20, Folder 347)
    - Memoranda, 1951-1960 (Box 20, Folder 348)
    - Leonard Menczer, 1959 (Box 21, Folder 349)
    - Isaias Mendoza del Salor, 1959 (Box 21, Folder 350)
    - George Meneely, 1959-1960 (Box 21, Folder 351)
    - Midwinter Medical Convention, 1955-1956 (Box 21, Folder 352)
    - Norman Miller, 1956-1957 (Box 21, Folder 353)
    - Eunice Miner, 1959 (Box 21, Folder 354)
    - Horace Miner, 1957-1958 (Box 21, Folder 355)
    - Miscellaneous, n.d. (Box 21, Folder 356)
    - Miscellaneous Data, n.d. (Box 21, Folder 357)
    - J. S. Mitchell, 1958 (Box 21, Folder 358)
    - Monozite Sands Study, 1957-1960 (Box 21, Folder 359)
      Radiation in Kerala. Charles Dunham, Bentley Glass.
    - Frederick J. Moore, 1960 (Box 21, Folder 360)
    - Robert S. Morrison, 1960-1964 (Box 21, Folder 361)
    - Thomas Murray, 1959-1960 (Box 21, Folder 362)
      Arms control.
    - T. Nakayama, 1955-1956 (Box 21, Folder 363)
    - National Academy of Sciences - National Research Council, 1955-1963 (Box 21, Folder 364)
      Fallout study. Warren Weaver.
    - National Academy of Sciences - National Research Council, 1955-1963 (Box 21, Folder 365)
    - National Academy of Sciences - National Research Council, 1955-1963 (Box 21, Folder 366)
    - National Academy of Sciences - National Research Council - Ad Hoc Conference, 1956 (Box 22, Folder 367)
      Information Retrieval. Alberto Thompson.
    - National Academy of Sciences - Biological Effects of Atomic Radiation, Pathology Committee, 1955-1961 (Box 22, Folder 368)
      Subcommittee on Radiobiology. Ernest Pollard, James Nickson.
    - National Academy of Sciences - Biological Effects of Atomic Radiation, Pathology Committee, 1955-1961 (Box 22, Folder 369)
    - National Academy of Sciences - Biological Effects of Atomic Radiation, Pathology Committee Reports, n.d. (Box 22, Folder 370)
    - National Academy of Sciences - Committee on Atomic Casualties, 1955-1956 (Box 22, Folder 371)
    - National Committee on Radiation Protection, 1953-1961 (Box 22, Folder 372)
      S. Taylor. Manuals; maximum permissible dose levels.
    - National Committee on Radiation Protection, 1953-1961 (Box 22, Folder 373)
    - National Committee on Radiation Protection, 1953-1961 (Box 22, Folder 374)
    - National Committee on Radiation Protection, 1953-1961 (Box 22, Folder 375)
    - National Committee on Radiation Protection, 1964-1966 (Box 23, Folder 376)
    - National Committee on Radiation Protection - Reports, n.d. (Box 23, Folder 377)
    - National Institute for Disaster Mobilization, 1956-April 1960 (Box 23, Folder 378)
      Civil defense; library; shelters; clearing house; Reuhenhausen report. S. A. Anthony, Formerly Civil Defense Research Associates.
    - National Institute for Disaster Mobilization, 1956-April 1960 (Box 23, Folder 379)
    - National Institute for Disaster Mobilization, 1956-April 1960 (Box 23, Folder 380)
    - National Institute for Disaster Mobilization, 1956-April 1960 (Box 23, Folder 381)
    - National Institute for Disaster Mobilization, 1956-April 1960 (Box 23, Folder 382)
    - National Institute for Disaster Mobilization, 1956-April 1960 (Box 23, Folder 383)
    - National Institute for Disaster Mobilization, May 1960-1963 (Box 24, Folder 384)
    - National Institute for Disaster Mobilization, May 1960-1963 (Box 24, Folder 385)
    - National Institute for Disaster Mobilization - Reports, n.d. (Box 24, Folder 386)
    - National Institute for Disaster Mobilization - Reports, n.d. (Box 24, Folder 387)
    - National Institute for Disaster Mobilization - "The Forum", 1960-1965 (Box 24, Folder 388)
    - National Institute for Disaster Mobilization - Finances, 1957-1960 (Box 24, Folder 389)
    - James Neel, 1959 (Box 25, Folder 390)
    - New York University, 1960 (Box 25, Folder 391)
    - James Nickson, 1959 (Box 25, Folder 392)
    - Nuclide Analysis Associates, n.d. (Box 25, Folder 393)
    - Oak Ridge National Laboratory, n.d. (Box 25, Folder 394)
    - Walter Oliver, 1956 (Box 25, Folder 396)
    - Francisco Ortigas, 1956 (Box 25, Folder 397)
    - Frederick Osborn, 1960 (Box 25, Folder 398)
    - Overseas Press Club, 1957 (Box 25, Folder 399)
    - Pan American Sanitary Bureau - World Health Organization (WHO) Yellow Fever Conference, 1954 (Box 25, Folder 400)
    - Thomas Parron, 1960 (Box 25, Folder 401)
    - Herman Pearse, 1959 (Box 25, Folder 402)
    - Paul B. Pearson, 1955-1960 (Box 25, Folder 403)
    - William Penney, 1960 (Box 25, Folder 404)
    - Pergamon, Press, 1955-1957 (Box 25, Folder 405)
    - Pergamon, Press, 1955-1957 (Box 25, Folder 406)
    - "Progress in Nuclear Energy" Series, n.d. (Box 25, Folder 407)
      Editorial advisory board; "International Journal of Applied Radioactivity and Isotopes;" proofs. Ian R. Maxwell.
    - Pergamon Press - Austin Brues, 1955-1956 (Box 25, Folder 408)
    - Pergamon Press - T. C. Carter, 1955 (Box 25, Folder 409)
    - Pergamon Press - A. J. Cipriani, 1955-1956 (Box 25, Folder 410)
    - Pergamon Press - C. L. Comar, 1955-1956 (Box 25, Folder 411)
    - Pergamon Press - G. Failla, 1955-1956 (Box 25, Folder 412)
    - Pergamon Press - Alexander Hollander, 1955-1956 (Box 25, Folder 413)
    - Pergamon Press - W. V. Mayneord, 1956 (Box 26, Folder 414)
    - Pergamon Press - Joseph Ross, 1955-1956 (Box 26, Folder 415)
    - Pergamon Press - R. Scott Russell, 1955 (Box 26, Folder 416)
    - Jesse Perkinson, 1960-1964 (Box 26, Folder 417)
      International Atomic Energy Agency Conference on reactors.
    - G. W. Petrie, 1959 (Box 26, Folder 418)
    - Photosynthesis - Solar Energy Project, 1956 (Box 26, Folder 419)
      Proposed Puerto Rico Institute.
    - "Post Graduate Medicine", 1955 (Box 26, Folder 420)
    - Eric Predie, 1959 (Box 26, Folder 421)
    - Puerto Rico, 1957-1965 (Box 26, Folder 422)
    - Radiation Research Society, 1960 (Box 26, Folder 423)
    - Eduardo Ramos, 1959 (Box 26, Folder 424)
    - Representation, 1955-1958 (Box 26, Folder 425)
    - Rift Valley Fever, 1952 (Box 26, Folder 426)
    - The Rockefeller Foundation - Medical Education and Public Health (MEPH) Drafts, 1955-1957 (Box 26, Folder 427)
    - The Rockefeller Foundation - Medical Education and Public Health (MEPH) Drafts, 1955-1957 (Box 26, Folder 428)
    - The Rockefeller Foundation - Medical Education and Public Health (MEPH) Drafts, 1955-1957 (Box 26, Folder 429)
    - The Rockefeller Foundation - Program, 1956-1959 (Box 27, Folder 430)
    - The Rockefeller Foundation - Program, 1956-1959 (Box 27, Folder 431)
    - The Rockefeller Foundation - Program, 1956-1959 (Box 27, Folder 432)
    - The Rockefeller Foundation - Program in Nursing, 1955-1956 (Box 27, Folder 433)
    - Rockefeller Institute, 1957-1958 (Box 27, Folder 434)
    - Joseph Ross, 1956-1960 (Box 27, Folder 435)
    - Dean Rusk, 1960-1961 (Box 27, Folder 436)
    - Howard A. Rusk, 1955-1960 (Box 27, Folder 437)
    - Scott Russell, 1961 (Box 27, Folder 438)
    - Russian Translations of Scientific Literature, 1956-1958 (Box 27, Folder 439)
    - John Rust, 1960 (Box 27, Folder 440)
      Radiation in Brazil.
    - Pierre Ryckmans, 1956 (Box 27, Folder 441)
    - Kiyoshi Saito, 1959 (Box 27, Folder 442)
      Strontium 90, Cesium 137, bone samples.
    - Peter Sammartino, 1960 (Box 27, Folder 443)
    - Scarsdale Adult School, 1957 (Box 27, Folder 444)
      Science-Economics Work Shop lecture. Joint Council on Economic Education.
    - Walther Schurr, 1960 (Box 27, Folder 445)
    - Science-Economics Workshop, 1958 (Box 27, Folder 446)
    - Virgil Scott, 1961-1966 (Box 27, Folder 447)
    - Wendell G. Scott, 1961-1963 (Box 27, Folder 448)
    - Second International Conference on the Peaceful Uses of Atomic Energy, 1958-1959 (Box 27, Folder 449)
      John Loutit.
    - Second International Congress of Radiation Research, 1960 (Box 27, Folder 450)
    - Seminar on Use of Vital Health Statistics for Genetic and Radiation Studies, 1960 (Box 27, Folder 451)
    - Edith Shaw, 1955-1959 (Box 27, Folder 452)
    - Rolf Sievert, 1959-1960 (Box 27, Folder 453)
    - R. A. Silow, 1960 (Box 28, Folder 454)
      Radioactivity in food and agriculture.
    - Slides and Tables (Box 28, Folder 455)
    - W. J. Smart, 1958 (Box 28, Folder 456)
    - Gerald Smith, 1956 (Box 28, Folder 457)
    - Kenneth Smithburn, 1954-1956 (Box 28, Folder 458)
    - Fred Soper, 1955-1960 (Box 28, Folder 459)
    - Southern Methodist Association, 1960 (Box 28, Folder 460)
    - J. Souto, 1959-1960 (Box 28, Folder 461)
    - John D. Spikes, 1959 (Box 28, Folder 462)
    - Ernest L. Stebbins, 1959-1960 (Box 28, Folder 463)
    - F. L. Stone, 1960 (Box 28, Folder 464)
    - Lewis Strauss, 1955-1960 (Box 28, Folder 465)
      Hearings.
    - Margaret Strong, 1955-1956 (Box 28, Folder 466)
      Mayan Indians.
    - Masashi Suzuki, 1959 (Box 28, Folder 467)
    - William Sweet, 1960 (Box 28, Folder 468)
    - Elizabeth Taber, 1956 (Box 28, Folder 469)
    - Gerald Tape, 1960 (Box 28, Folder 470)
    - Geroge V. Taplin, 1960 (Box 28, Folder 471)
    - Angus Taylor, 1955-1956 (Box 28, Folder 472)
      Marine biology.
    - Grant Taylor, 1959-1963 (Box 28, Folder 473)
      Biomedical program development, pediatrics project.
    - Lauriston S. Taylor, 1959-1960 (Box 28, Folder 474)
    - Richard M. Taylor, 1962-1966 (Box 28, Folder 475)
    - Taylor University, 1958-1960 (Box 28, Folder 476)
    - Teletherapy Radiation Sources, 1958-1959 (Box 28, Folder 477)
    - M. E. Tennant, 1955 (Box 28, Folder 478)
    - Roland Thomas, 1955-1956 (Box 28, Folder 479)
    - Oliver Townsend, 1960 (Box 28, Folder 480)
    - Toxicology and Safety Evaluations, 1956-1957 (Box 28, Folder 481)
    - Cornelius Traeger, 1960 (Box 28, Folder 482)
    - B. F. Trum, 1958-1959 (Box 28, Folder 483)
      Civil defense.
    - United Nations Committee on the Effects of Atomic Radiation, 1955-1960 (Box 28, Folder 484)
    - United Nations Education Scientific and Cultural Organization (UNESCO) - Seventh National Conference on Latin America, Subcommittee on Science, 1958-1959 (Box 28, Folder 485)
    - U.S. Naval Research Laboratory, 1961 (Box 28, Folder 486)
    - University of Michigan Law School - Atomic Energy Advisory Committee, 1959-1960 (Box 28, Folder 487)
      William H. Berman, Lee Hydeman, Maritime Study; research on legal and policy problems in domestic and international aspects of atomic energy.
    - University of Michigan Medical School, 1959 (Box 29, Folder 488)
    - University of Pittsburgh - Seminar on Public Health, 1957 (Box 29, Folder 489)
    - J. Van der Schueren, 1960 (Box 29, Folder 490)
    - J. J. Van Rysinge, 1960 (Box 29, Folder 491)
    - H. van Waeyenbergh, 1959 (Box 29, Folder 492)
    - Vanderbilt Symposium, 1959-1960 (Box 29, Folder 493)
      Radioactivity; implications for the future; industry, panelist.
    - Herbert Vetter, 1959 (Box 29, Folder 494)
    - Jose R. Vivos, 1960 (Box 29, Folder 495)
    - Earl Voss, 1960 (Box 29, Folder 496)
      Nuclear test ban history.
    - Robert Wagner, 1960 (Box 29, Folder 497)
    - Andrew J. Warren, 1950 (Box 29, Folder 498)
    - Shields Warren, 1959-1960 (Box 29, Folder 499)
    - R. S. Watson, 1960 (Box 29, Folder 500)
    - Robert B. Watson, 1955-1965 (Box 29, Folder 501)
    - Warren Weaver, 1955-1959 (Box 29, Folder 502)
    - Warren Weaver, 1955-1959 (Box 29, Folder 503)
    - Alvin Weinberg, 1960 (Box 29, Folder 504)
    - John M. Weir, 1960-1965 (Box 29, Folder 505)
    - Charles Weller, 1957 (Box 29, Folder 506)
    - Weller Lecture, 1956-1958 (Box 30, Folder 507)
      "Role of the Pathologist in Modern Medicine"
    - Warner Wells, 1956 (Box 30, Folder 508)
    - Werner-Gren Foundation, 1955-1960 (Box 30, Folder 509)
      Anthropology; symposium participant.
    - Kenneth Wernimont, 1964 (Box 30, Folder 510)
    - West African Council for Medical Research, 1960 (Box 30, Folder 511)
    - M. R. Westmorland, 1966 (Box 30, Folder 512)
    - Carroll Wilson, 1959 (Box 30, Folder 513)
    - D. Bruce Wilson, 1960 (Box 30, Folder 514)
    - "Who's Who in America", n.d. (Box 30, Folder 515)
    - Women's City Club of New York, 1959-1960 (Box 30, Folder 516)
    - Harland Wood, 1960 (Box 30, Folder 517)
    - Nathan Woodruff, 1960 (Box 30, Folder 518)
    - World Health Organization (WHO) Expert Advisory Committee on Radiation Mutations, 1957-1965 (Box 30, Folder 519)
    - World Health Organization (WHO) Expert Committee on Professional and Technical Education, 1957-1958 (Box 30, Folder 520)
    - C. Brooke Worth, 1960 (Box 30, Folder 521)
    - John B. Youmans, 1960 (Box 30, Folder 522)
    - Ray Zintz, 1958-1961 (Box 30, Folder 523)
- Articles, Speeches, Manuscripts, 2
  This series is arranged alphabetically.
  The items in this series are authored or co-authored by John C. Bugher.
  - Bibliography, n.d. (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - "Agricultural Radiobiology and the National Welfare", 1962 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - "Alan Gregg", 1957 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - "Antigenicity of Yellow Fever Vaccine Virus (17D) Following 57 Subcultures...", 1944 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - "The Application of Harmonic Analysis to Biting Cycle Studies of Mosquitoes.", n.d. (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - "Atomic Energy in Medicine", 1956 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - "Biologic Effects and Mechanism of Injury", 1953 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - "Biological Effects of Radiation", 1955 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - "Biological and Medical Applications of Atomic Energy to Civil Defense", 1954 (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - "Biology of Radiation", 1958 (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - "Changing Aspects of Public Health", 1959 (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - "Changing Patterns in Public Health", 1956 (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - "Characteristics of Collodion Membranes for Ultrafiltration", 1953 (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - "Comments by the Advisory Committee for Biology and Medicine...", 1959 (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - "Dedication of the Cobalt Teletherapy Unit, Montefiore Hospital", 1953 (Box 1, Folder 15)
  - "Dedication of the Indian Atomic Energy Facility, Bombay", 1957 (Box 1, Folder 16)